Rochester, New York and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO Records 6239
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Subject Files. S-W.. (Box 13)
  - Union Yes: Campaign (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - United Farm Workers (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - United States Post Office (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - United Way (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - United Way '95, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - UW, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    March 20. 1997
  - VDT/RSI Campaign 1991 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Voting Records, Senate and State (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - WACK Radio Show (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - WXXI (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - WXXI (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Wegman Foundation (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Educ. Comm. Wegman Fund Grant (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Work in Progress (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Worker Adjustment and Retaining Notification Act (WARN) (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - WTTW Conf. (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Worker's Comp. (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Worker's Comp. '93 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - WMO '89 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Workers Memorial Day 1990 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - WMD 1991 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Workers Mem. Day '92, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - WMD - 1993 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - WMD '94, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - WMD '95, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - WMO '96, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Wrkrs. Mem 1997 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Working Women (Box 13, Folder 38)